No other days in Yokohama underground
society produced as many corpses as those 88 did.
Many organizations were
involved in that bloodbath.
The Dragon Head Conflict
The night before its conclusion
This is sickening.
Corpses, no matter which way I look.
You're lucky to be alive in this situation.
Odasaku.
Dazai, where are you?
I have a feeling I know what you're up to,
but you need to run.
It's not going to be safe there for long.
Piss off, scrub.
Hi, Chuuya. You're in range of the enemy.
Take some bullets and die, thanks.
Shut up.
Damn gifted.
He thinks he's the shit.
It would have been more amusing if you'd
been struck by lightning and killed.
Shut it, Dazai.
You're five minutes late.
Because of that, I got smacked
three more times than I needed to.
I might as well finish you off.
I'm not the one you need to kill.
Look at all this trash.
Clean it up, please.
You're prepared for this, aren't you?
Come to think of it,
I have a debt to repay you.
It'll be mine.
It won't be mine.
Those jewels are all real.
He could have made a woman really happy.
It won't be mine.
It's not much fun seeing
these readings come true.
Starting an organization hasn't
helped me get what I want.
Give me back my friends.
Welcome, boring guest.
I don't expect you to give me what I desire.
Die now, as they did.
All your friends killed themselves.
Boring people are boring, even in death.
You...
Don't stop me.
Oh, dear.
Corruption, huh?
This is too much fun.
The day world and the night world
An armed agency working in the twilight
Gifted Group:
The Armed Detective Agency
Nakajima Atsushi
Special Ability:
Beast Beneath the Moonlight
[18 years old. Armed Detective Agency employee.]
Taken under the Agency's wing when he was found
struggling after his time at an orphanage.
Protagonist of the story.
Dazai Osamu
Special Ability:
No Longer Human
[22 years old. Armed Detective Agency employee.]
Atsushi's mentor, as he was the one to scout him.
A suicide maniac and bandage-wasting machine.
Izumi Kyouka
Special Ability:
Demon Snow
[14 years old. Armed Detective Agency employee.]
Former assassin for the Port Mafia.
Likes rabbits and tofu.
Kunikida Doppo
Special Ability:
Doppo Poet
[22 years old. Armed Detective Agency employee.]
An idealist who never accepts half-measures.
Meticulous
Miyazawa Kenji
Special Ability:
Be Not Defeated By The Rain
[14 years old. Armed Detective Agency employee.]
An artless boy, born in the countryside.
Loves cows, eats cows.
Edogawa Rampo
Special Ability:
Ultra Deduction
[26 years old. Armed Detective Agency employee.]
An excellent detective with
ultimate powers of deduction.
Motto: "All's well that's well by me."
Yosano Akiko
Special Ability:
Thou Shalt Not Die
[25 years old. Armed Detective Agency doctor.]
Skilled in healing all kinds of exterior wounds.
Passionate about dissections.
Tanizaki Junichirou
Special Ability:
Light Snow
[18 years old. Armed Detective Agency employee.]
A slightly timid Agency employee.
Cohabits with his sister. (?)
Fukuzawa Yukichi
Special Ability:
All Men Are Created Equal
[45 years old. Armed Detective Agency president.]
The founder of the Detective Agency,
formerly known as the Silver Wolf.
An extremely capable martial artist.
Port Mafia
A violent organization that represents the very darkness of Yokohama.
Runs the city and controls both politics and economy.
Is ruthless against anyone who opposes them in either mainstream or underground society.
Akutagawa Ryunosuke
Special Ability:
Rashoumon
[20 years old. Port Mafia executive.]
A battle-oriented gifted
with the nickname Silent Rabid Dog.
Previously fought almost to the death
with Nakajima Atsushi.
Nakahara Chuuya
Special Ability:
For The Tainted Sorrow
[22 years old. Port Mafia executive.]
A fancy hat, formerly called
"Double Black" alongside Dazai.
Mori Ougai
Special Ability:
Vita Sexualis
[40 years old. Port Mafia boss.]
The cold, calculating mastermind
overseeing this band of cruel gifted.
Has a lolita complex.
Sakaguchi Ango
Special Ability:
Discourse on Decadence
[26 years old. Ministry of Internal Affairs,
Gifted Special Operations Division Assistant Counselor.]
In charge of maintaining national security
in light of matters to do with gifted activity.
Perpetually sleep deprived.
Fyodor D.
Special Ability:
Crime and Punishment
[Age unknown.]
Leader of the underground organization
"Rats in the House of the Dead".
Bungo Stray Dogs
Six years later...
I never knew this place existed in Yokohama.
Nakajima Atsushi-kun.
Yes?
Do you know whose grave this is?
No.
But it's someone dear to you, right?
What makes you think that?
I've never seen you pay a visit to a grave.
Does it look like I'm
visiting a grave to you?
It does. Why?
Odasaku!
Odasaku...
What am I supposed to do?
Be on the side that saves people.
If it doesn't matter either way,
be a good person.
Save the weak, and protect the orphans.
There's little difference between
justice and evil to you, is there?
That's at least a little more beautiful.
How can you be so sure?
I can.
More than anyone.
I'm your friend, after all.
Was it someone you were in love with?
If it was a woman I loved,
I'd have died with her.
Oh, yeah, I guess you would have.
Did you say something?
Oh, no.
Nothing.
He was a friend.
The man who gave me a reason to quit
the Port Mafia and join the Detective Agency.
Without him, I may have stayed in the Mafia,
murdering people.
I'm kidding.
I bet Kunikida-kun told you
to come find me, didn't he?
Yes.
He said there's an important meeting.
Pass.
I've been wanting to try
a new suicide technique.
Again?
Jeez.
Kunikida-san's going to
give me an earful again.
Dihua Street, Taipei
Play
This is footage from a security
camera in Taipei, Taiwan.
As you can see, the fog erupted in
a matter of minutes, and vanished.
But this isn't a weather anomaly.
Suspicious bodies were
discovered after the fog.
This burnt corpse.
Terrible.
Kunikida...
Yes?
This person's gifted.
You're correct, Rampo-san.
He was a well-known fire-wielding
gifted in his area.
Age: Approx. 34
Taipei - Dihua Street
Death by immolation
This is Singapore, a year ago.
Sure enough, a dense fog emerged.
Another suspicious corpse
was discovered after it dissipated.
He was a card-wielding gifted.
A talented assassin.
Detroit, half a year ago.
Another body discovered after the fog.
As you can imagine, she was
an ice-wielding gifted.
In other words, after the strange fog,
these gifted people across the world
died by their own abilities.
Is the fog somehow related?
There are 128 confirmed cases that are
thought to be of the same nature.
More than five hundred have died.
The Gifted Special Operations Division
calls this series of events
the "Serial Gifted Suicide Incident".
Speaking of suicide...
Where's that fool Dazai, Atsushi?
He said he was going to pass, because he
came up with a new suicide technique.
That bonehead!
I see.
What are you doing, Rampo-san?
It's a secret.
So any gifted who touches
that fog kills themselves?
I'll never let you do that.
I'm never going to let you kill
yourself and leave me behind.
So, what does this have to do with us?
There's more to this than just,
"Let's be careful, because we're gifted, too," right?
The Special Operations Division has
requested that we investigate.
We've received information that a man thought
to be involved in these serial
suicides is in Yokohama.
We've been asked to capture him.
This is that man.
Name: Shibusawa
Tatsuhiko
Age: 29
Sex: Unknown
Height: Unknown
Weight: Unknown
Special Abilities: Unknown
Nationality: Unknown
Shibusawa Tatsuhiko. Twenty-nine.
All we know is that he has
some kind of special ability,
and that he goes by the
street name "Collector".
Is something wrong?
No, nothing.
The Armed Detective Agency
will accept this job.
Gifted are the most direct
victims of this case.
This is also important to protect
the lives of the Agency.
More than anything, I get the sense that
this is going to cause broader public harm.
The Detective Agency will hereby commit all
of its resources to investigating this man.
Kunikida-san, what do you think?
About what?
Is serial suicide even a thing?
I can't say.
Supposing they have the ability
to control people psychologically,
the international investigation agencies
would have information on someone that powerful.
I hope we can get some
more detailed information
out of the Special Operations
Division agent we're about to meet.
Perfectly on schedule.
Kunikida-san!
It's the Special Operations Division agent.
He's dead.
What's the matter?
Did the murderer leave this behind?
An apple?
Kunikida-san...
Why an apple?
How should I know?
What shall we toast to today?
Shouldn't we wait for Ango to arrive?
Let's chat, then.
I heard something interesting recently.
Have you heard of apple suicide?
Apple suicide?
Yup, apple suicide.
Oh, you mean Cinderella.
Cinderella...
I didn't expect you to say that.
I never get bored of
talking to you, Odasaku.
Just for your information, it was
Snow White who ate the poison apple.
And it wasn't suicide in her case.
I see.
I got it wrong.
No, hang on.
Maybe she did commit suicide.
Maybe she took a bite of the
apple knowing it was poisoned.
Why?
Despair.
Despair in having been given
poison by her mother.
No...
Maybe it was a more nebulous despair.
Despair intrinsic to this world.
That would be interesting,
if it were the case.
I met an interesting gifted recently.
He makes people commit apple suicide.
It might become popular
in Yokohama someday, too.
Suicide, you mean?
Yeah.
Wouldn't it be beautiful?
You're an interesting one.
Your mind dances.
Nowhere as interesting as you.
Ango's late.
Ango's not coming.
Odasaku, what you said is true.
Being on the side that saves people
is definitely more beautiful...
if the goal is to continue living.
I'm off, now, Odasaku.
Dazai-kun.
Oh, Ango.
You're here.
Did you come for a drink?
No, I'm in the middle of work.
Work?
You were the one who brought Shibusawa
Tatsuhiko here to Yokohama, aren't you?
Are you plotting to start
a mass suicide here?
Do you think you can catch me?
Get out, you good-for-nothing!
No orphanage would welcome the likes of you!
The world would be a better place
if you'd just die in a ditch somewhere!
What the...?
You don't belong anywhere in this world.
I was dreaming.
Can I come in?
Yeah.
Are you okay?
Why?
You sounded like you were
having a really bad dream.
Yeah.
I had a bit of a nightmare.
Wait, Kyouka-chan?!
Was there fog in your dream?
Is this...?
My phone's not working.
Mine, neither.
Could this be the fog that apparently
makes gifted people kill themselves?
Let's go to the Agency.
R-Right now?
Th-The fog might clear up eventually.
Um...
Kyouka-chan...
Kyouka-chan!
Where's the driver?
What's going on?
Kyouka-chan...
Silence dominated.
It was as if every person
had vanished from the city.
Get out, you good-for-nothing!
You don't belong anywhere in this world.
Kyouka-chan...
I feel fierce bloodlust.
Kyouka-chan!
Is this another suicide
by special ability?
But I don't see a body.
Let's go, Kyouka-chan.
Beast Beneath the Moonlight!
Demon Snow!
Kunikida-san.
Atsushi.
That wound...
Did you get shot?
I got the bullet out.
I'm fine.
More importantly, I know what's
causing the serial suicides.
Run!
Kunikida-san, hurry!
Kunikida-san!
Kyouka-chan?
Are you all right?
What happened?
I got hit by my own ability.
By your own ability...?
Demon Snow!
Get on!
Run, Atsushi!
Kunikida-san, what were you saying about
the cause of the suicides...?
The gifted didn't commit suicide.
They were killed by their own abilities.
Let's hurry to the agency.
What happened here?
The president's office!
Kunikida-san!
What is that?
We almost have a connection.
Keep this level steady.
Can you hear me?
President Fukuzawa, is that you?
It's Agent Kunikida.
You're with the Special Operations
Division, correct?
Special Operations Division?
I'm Sakaguchi Ango of the
Special Operations Division.
Kunikida-san, what is the
situation over there?
I'm here with Nakajima
Atsushi and Izumi Kyouka.
All other Agency staff
are currently missing.
Understood.
Our connection isn't stable.
I'll keep it short.
The fog phenomenon has
happened here in Yokohama.
No such vast fog exists on record.
It has stopped spreading, but the
entirety of Yokohama is engulfed.
Yokohama is currently disconnected
from the outside.
Almost everyone in Yokohama
is currently missing, or has vanished.
It appears that only the
gifted are present.
Which means you're in danger as well.
We can confirm.
Here in this fog, the gifted have been
separated from their special abilities.
The abilities attempt to kill
the gifted they belong to.
This could definitely be bad.
Fortunately, we've determined
the location of the gifted
who is most likely responsible
for this phenomenon.
He's in an abandoned high-rise called
Mukurotoride in the center of Yokohama.
Is it Shibusawa Tatsuhiko, after all?
I am making an important
request of the Agency.
Please eliminate the mastermind,
Shibusawa Tatsuhiko.
By any means necessary.
Also, note that Dazai-kun appears
to be with the mastermind.
Dazai is?
He's been captured?
We need to act,
before Yokohama is annihilated.
You're our only hope.
He's here.
You two go on ahead.
I'll stop him myself.
But, Kunikida-san...
There's no way you're going to win
against your own ability.
It's not a matter of winning.
It's a matter of having the will to fight.
Prevailing against myself.
That's what I've always done.
What the...?
We are an armed detective agency.
Take this.
I don't need one.
His special ability won't let him make any
weapons larger than the size of the notebook.
Escape out the back door
while I draw him in.
Now!
I trust we've determined the
location of Gifted Number A5158.
Yes.
Please send a message.
What shall we say?
"Pay your debt to doc glasses."
Kunikida-san!
Kunikida-san's okay, right?
Our priority right now is to
eliminate Shibusawa Tatsuhiko.
Shibusawa Tatsuhiko.
I wonder what Shibusawa Tatsuhiko is like.
You say "eliminate," but there's no need to
kill anyone, no matter how bad they are.
We just need to capture him.
I'm sure Dazai-san will help
us once we get him out.
Yeah.
We can manage if we can save Dazai-san.
Dazai-san will know what to do.
Dazai-kun,
don't you get bored looking at that?
Bored?
Yeah, it's boring.
A sea of white and nothingness.
A nondescript world.
Tonight, all of Yokohama's special
abilities will become mine.
Once again, no one will emerge
whose intellect surpasses mine,
who will defy my expectations.
How boring.
I used to be bored, as you are.
How did you overcome it?
It's quicker to show you than to tell you.
See? Case in point: you don't know
what my true intentions are.
Am I helping you?
Am I going to use you and betray you?
You're the only one who
thinks you can't be read.
It seems you do need salvation.
Who do you propose could save me?
Who knows.
An angel?
Or a demon?
If you ask me, both of your
intentions are obvious.
You'll never write a good
play with such lies.
You've lost the audience, too.
Demon Fyodor-kun.
As my collaborator, I'm going
to have you dance as well.
Collaborator?
I think he's the most likely to betray you.
You're correct, indeed.
No one has surpassed my
expectations thus far.
I have my hopes up for you.
Of course, it's the gifted of this
town that I feel most sorry for.
No matter which of the three of us prevails,
they will all perish.
What am I going to do if I
never get my ability back?
I-Is it safe to drive so fast in this fog?
I have all of Yokohama's roads memorized.
That has nothing to do with my skills as
an assassin or with my special abilities.
When I first learned that I'd turned
into a tiger and gone on a rampage,
I wished my ability would disappear.
I never thought I'd be
attacked by that tiger.
Demon Snow killed my parents.
I've never thought of her as a friend.
If she opposes me, I'll defeat her.
She's here.
The safety!
Go!
Hurry!
You...
Akutagawa!
What a pathetic weapon.
No pea shooter is going
to have an effect on her.
Amusing.
Let's see who comes out on top.
Now isn't the time for that!
There should be a secret passage
nearby for the Mafia brass.
Come, weretiger.
Hey!
Go!
I'll be there, I promise!
All right.
Kyouka-chan!
This emergency passage was made
in case of a gifted attack.
The fog won't reach us here.
What is that fog?
It's the dragon's breath.
Dragon?
Kyouka, with neither of
us having our abilities,
you could kill me with your assassin skills.
What's wrong?
Didn't you have a score to settle with me?
Kyouka-chan doesn't think
anything of you anymore!
Want to end this while we don't
have our abilities?
You know how to get our abilities back?
I know of a way.
What?!
Defeat the ability,
and it'll return to its owner.
Are you that uninformed?
What is your plan?
It's probably the same as ours.
No...
Shibusawa?
I'm going to shred his
organs and end his life.
Is there any other way to save Yokohama?
We won't kill.
That's not what the Detective Agency does.
That's laughable.
You're quite something, weretiger.
What?!
Kyouka understands what this job entails.
She's former Port Mafia, after all.
I left to live in the light of day.
I quit the Port Mafia to
join the Detective Agency.
The Mafia's killings and the
Agency's killings are different.
Kyouka-chan...
If it had happened before
Dazai-san joined the enemy,
we may have stopped the fog
before we had to kill.
Dazai-san joined the enemy?!
Indeed.
He allied himself with the
enemy of his own volition.
Dazai-san would never do such a thing!
He already betrayed the Port Mafia.
I'm going to be the one to kill Dazai-san.
Do you think you can kill Dazai-san?
If he's going to fall into enemy hands,
I'd rather kill him myself.
I won't let you kill Dazai-san.
I can't go with you.
I'm going with him.
My collection room.
Welcome to Draconia.
So these are all crystallized abilities.
I'm impressed you gathered all this.
A splendid collection.
The devil would be jealous.
That would make you death's rat,
here to sell information to the devil.
Most of this collection was gathered using
information I bought from you.
Thanks to you,
I was able to create this massive volume of fog,
large enough to engulf the whole city.
But how did you gather all that information?
Every city is filled with rats.
Meow.
Here comes another.
Somewhere in Yokohama, a gifted has died.
Alas, without the one special ability
that belongs here, none of this matters.
No matter how many I gather.
Kyouka-chan, why are you following this guy?
He has information.
We can use the Mafia's secret passage.
More than anything,
he's taken his ability back.
He's a powerful asset.
Our goal of eliminating
Shibusawa is the same.
But...
It looks like you're still holding
on to your mother's cell phone.
Mother?
You haven't even been told about that?
I haven't...
What's the shortest route?
Zero five zero five.
No wonder they can sense my presence.
I'll help.
No.
I've wandered many a night and slain
many an enemy to prove my might.
But I hadn't thought such an enemy,
worthy of fighting and being defeated,
would be so near.
Don't act on your own.
We each have something we need to be doing.
Do what you need to be doing.
Kyouka-chan!
To me, people are nothing but machines of flesh,
behaving in identifiable ways.
But there is just one person
I fail to comprehend.
Myself.
Don't you have any friends?
I don't need friends.
I understand everyone's minds, after all.
I will surely go to the world beyond,
between my lines, past the blank spaces.
You wouldn't be saying that
if you actually had friends.
That time will soon come.
For all of this here, Yokohama's special
abilities are to become mine.
Do you think there's even one person who
can surpass their own special abilities?
The Rashoumon attack is one where cloth is
turned to a blade and sent flying at the enemy.
Thus, so long as one is outside
of its reach, they are safe.
Shit.
How do I defeat it?
Do I just need to destroy that thing?
Dammit!
No one can win against their
own special ability, after all.
Demon Snow killed my mother.
But if I defeat her, I'll merge
with her and become a demon again.
Just as I hoped.
What?
I'd expect as much from
my own ability.
But...
Good.
That's where you belong.
Demon Snow is an
embodiment of slaughter.
And yet...
And yet, I...
And yet you want to use that power
for the sake of others, don't you?
Kyouka.
Kyouka-chan!
Shatter the crystal on her forehead!
Here it comes.
What is?
A5158.
You've got some nerve, calling me out
like some take-out delivery boy.
May we have some time alone?
This is a government facility.
You don't expect to get
away with this, do you?
I'll be the one to decide if I do or not.
Not you.
You have a debt to me.
No, you have a debt with me.
What are you talking about?
Don't act dumb. Do you think I don't know?
It's what happened six years ago.
How's your wound?
I'm fine.
Once I have my strength back,
it'll recover on its own with my tiger healing ability.
Mukurotoride.
That's where Dazai-san is.
We have to help Dazai-san.
He'll know what to do.
You got your ability back, huh?
My tiger's healing ability hasn't come back.
I defeated the tiger... Why...?
You got your ability back, too, huh?
Why am I the only one who hasn't?
Fool! Do you still not understand?
What...
What the hell?!
Akutagawa!
Explain!
Hey!
You're too hurt.
Rest here.
Kyouka-chan?
I'm sorry I never told you.
I didn't want you to know.
About what?
That I control Demon Snow with my phone.
That I actually didn't want to hate her.
I'll complete the mission.
Wait!
Kyouka-chan.
Kyouka-chan!
That's why you're no good.
What do you mean?
It was you bureaucrats who sent Shibusawa
into the Dragon Head Conflict.
It was supposed to end the conflict
that had engulfed all of Yokohama.
But he never had any intention
of maintaining peace.
All you did was create more corpses.
You protected him anyway,
because he's a gifted
with the potential to stand up against
a nation-wide gifted takeover.
That's why, not only did you turn a blind eye
to all the corpses he'd produced
overseas, you covered it all up.
All for the peace in this nation.
Watch your mouth, doc glasses.
If you hadn't sent him out,
all six of my friends
would be alive right now.
Will you kill me?
I wouldn't mind.
I've been prepared ever since I'd
decided to ask for your assistance.
It's a deal, then.
I'll accept your job.
And you'll pay with your life.
All according to plan.
Yeah, all according to plan.
That was a pain in the ass,
getting in without making
him suspicious of us.
Say, what's the real reason
you teamed up with me?
Simply to see the world as it ought to be.
But wouldn't you agree that the more
entertainment there is, the better?
So the question is, who is the clown, huh?
I had no intention of making an ally of you,
but it was necessary to
make Shibusawa the clown.
He even has the Japanese government
by the balls, after all.
He was intent on creating the fog here in
Yokohama with or without your guidance, after all.
Here you are.
One is a crystal that summons all
the gifted as far as the eye can see here.
The other turns the abilities of
the gifted who touch it into crystals.
With these two crystals, we can
consume the entire collection,
starving the fog of an energy source
and rendering it unsustainable.
Now, first, use your nullification ability
to disable the shell that is the crystal,
and return the abilities
to their former state.
I hope Atsushi-kun and the others are safe.
Touch that, and it'll erase everything.
It'll all be over.
Didn't I tell you?
None will surpass my expectations.
I was certain I'd locked the door...
I see.
So this is where the betrayal happens.
Didn't I tell you?
The more entertainment, the better.
And?
What will you do next?
There is no next.
You alone have always been my target.
I thought this fruit knife wouldn't
do more than make me hurt.
But poison...
It's a lethal anesthetic.
Taste death. You've longed for it so dearly.
How could you?
This feels great.
With the owner dead,
the special ability leaves him.
This is the first time in my life
that my heart has raced so.
This isn't it!
What?
Don't open that door.
Though you have neither the
courage nor the dignity.
You've finally lost your tiger's ability.
Part with it and move on.
Don't worry, no one expects anything of you.
I won't listen to you.
Once you know, you can't
go back to not knowing.
If you've made it to the door,
it isn't locked.
Go of your own will, and die.
The merging ability and
the disabling ability.
With the two contrary abilities
becoming one, a singularity is born.
Even with Dazai's special ability,
what you really desire—
your lost memories — will never come back.
How do you know about that?!
Not to worry, I'll fill in the lines
that were blanked out for you.
That is death.
Do you remember anything?
I see...
This sensation...
I remember it.
That president doesn't understand
your special ability.
Your ability is rare,
even throughout the world.
It's the only special ability that
won the envy of all other gifted.
But perhaps, because of your youth,
your special ability is locked deep within you.
I can't pull it out, even with my fog.
So...
Now, surprise me.
Is this...
Right.
I remember, now.
That moment, I used my claws.
That moment, I hit the switch.
Because I heard your special ability was
one that guided the envy of all other gifted.
A Russian named Fyodor.
That's right.
That moment, you died.
And it was you, yourself,
who'd inherited your ability,
when you parted with your body.
You'd forgotten about your own death and
made a room to collect and manage yourself in.
That's who you are now.
That moment, I used my claws.
That's right.
That moment, you killed me.
With those claws of yours.
What do you expect?!
I wanted to live!
A boy always uses the claws
of a tiger in order to live!
It's the beginning of the end.
You're quite greedy, aren't you, Dazai-kun?
Even in death, you intend to see
this town to its demise, do you?
I'll tell you an interesting fact,
in celebration of you finding a friend in me.
Have you never thought about why my special
ability doesn't leave me in this fog?
I am crime.
I am punishment.
Did you know?
Crime and punishment are close friends.
Borders vanish.
Rooms awaken.
The incarnation of death, the master
of the ability-consuming fog...
Eat, howl, and make violence
as your instinct desires.
This is neither a loss of
control nor a singularity.
The dragon is the true form of
the chaos of special abilities.
Singularity anomaly readings are increasing.
Five times higher than six years ago.
Five point five.
Readings increasing.
They won't stop.
What is A5158's current location?
Get your shit together, scrub.
Chuuya-kun...
Dazai-kun is almost certainly
eliminated by now.
Do you understand what that means?
I don't care.
Are you sure?
You haven't taken your reward... My life.
Don't get cocky, asshole.
You were a lowly infiltrator six years ago.
No one lent you an ear when you opposed
employing Shibusawa, did they?
This is nothing but his bumbling.
That dimwit Dazai is inside there.
No doubt about it.
I need to give him a smack,
or I'll never get over it.
I'm hanging up.
I'm counting on you.
We're approaching the target.
You're that chick from way back.
Tsujimura.
Are you really going?
Yeah.
It's no use.
It's a gifted against a human.
That thing is a monster
beyond human comprehension.
Get overconfident and fight it,
and you'll die.
That's not a reason to
chicken out and go home.
Do you know when it's all right
to chicken out and go home?
I do not.
There is no such time.
Grantors of dark disgrace,
you need not wake me again.
Amazing.
It's all getting higher.
His special ability is gravity control.
In this state of contamination,
having become a slave to gravitons,
he can neither control nor disable it.
So he has no control of it until he dies?
Dazai-kun's nullification ability
is the only way to end it.
Without it, he's doomed.
No...
You used Corruption, believing in me?
How beautiful.
Yeah, I did.
I believed in your disgusting
vitality and craftiness.
That was a somewhat violent
way of waking Snow White.
You're the one who hid an antidote in your mouth,
knowing I'd punch you.
Let go, asshole.
Don't move.
The fog hasn't cleared.
I don't want to have to protect you from
your special ability in this situation.
It's still not over?
No, it's just beginning.
Shit.
I can't move a single finger.
I predicted this far.
But the rest is on them.
You act as though you know everything,
when in fact you know nothing.
The fog will spread unceasingly.
This planet will become a fruit
of death — a dead apple.
I have a modest gift for you.
A fragment of the crystal
for gathering abilities.
With this, you're the singularity.
I remember everything, now.
It wasn't the special
abilities that I sought.
It was the glimmer of the light
of the tenacious life force,
prevailing over my own special ability...
Over my own fate.
It was the light you'd shown me.
By killing me, your soul had proven
to me the strength of life.
Show me your light once more!
The fog has begun to spread!
Singularity variance immeasurable.
Expansion speed 100 kilometers.
At current rate, in an hour and thirty-five minutes,
the whole of the Kanto region will be engulfed.
In twelve hours and thirty-six minutes, all of Tokyo,
and in 168 hours the whole of
the planet will be covered.
Are you serious?
We have a call from the English
special operations organization.
It's the Clock Tower esquires...
Good day.
On behalf of the nations of Europe, my heart
goes out to your nation in this time of crisis.
On that note, in order to prevent it from
spreading throughout the rest of the world,
we have deployed a gifted with
an incineration ability.
Incineration ability...
When will they begin?
In exactly thirty minutes.
With the crack of dawn.
Yokohama's going to be incinerated.
Shibusawa, correct?
Rashoumon
Rashoumon!
Demonic...
Demonic
Armor
Armor!
So you lot are gifted.
"You lot"?
Why did you come?
I just want that man to live in the light.
I'll kill this man.
Demon Snow!
To think that two of you would
take back your special abilities.
We aren't the only two to have
taken our abilities back.
I expect that this, too, was within
your calculations, Dazai-kun.
Though I don't have time to
worry about others right now.
I love you, Rintarou.
You're too adorable, Elise-chan.
I can't bring myself to shred you up.
Now, what is the optimal
solution in this situation?
A swordsman with skill equal to mine.
You may have no equal in skill,
but you're far too proper.
With no guile in your sword,
you will never defeat me.
Fukuzawa-dono.
What a coincidence, Mori-sensei.
Are you having a problem?
I've just had a glimpse of a solution.
Excellent.
Is it not at times like these
that your daily actions speak?
I thought it was just your scalpel.
I'll be careful from now on.
No mercy, even for an endearing girl.
The lone swordsman, Silver Wolf.
You are indeed guilty.
That was nothing but a fiend.
Hey, Rintarou!
What the heck are you doing,
leaving me behind?!
It's the real Elise-chan.
I don't believe you!
I think she's a fiend either way.
What's the light of life?
I don't have any light of life.
When I lost my tiger abilities to the fog,
I was honestly relieved
that now I didn't have to
hurt the people around me.
That the tiger and I are actually separate creatures.
But... the tiger once helped me.
I've already passed through death.
How do you kill something
that's already dead?
You abomination!
No matter where I run, the tiger follows.
It's the same as the way I can't
escape the beating of my own heart.
For you're my strength to keep living.
I hear you well, now.
I understand your words well.
I know.
I know everyone's souls are on fire.
I'll say the same to you.
Hurry up, or I'm leaving you behind.
Come, tiger!
I've taken the light of your lives,
but that light isn't enough.
Dragon Tiger is a well-deserved name.
The Russian who told me of
your existence told me
that the dragon is the true form
of the chaos of special abilities.
Then, as you are the one who embodies the tiger,
you are the antithesis of all special abilities.
Took you long enough.
Are you going to kill me again,
Nakajima Atsushi-kun?
I'm simply going to return
something to where it belongs.
Don't be mistaken.
I'm not stopping you.
Good, Atsushi-kun.
You are indeed special.
I'm definitely not bored anymore.
Demon Snow!
The three of us need to
combine our strength.
Otherwise we can't secure
our place of being.
You can call Demon Snow again, right?
Kyouka, weretiger...
You understand what you
need to do, don't you?
Yeah, I know.
Kyouka-chan.
You said you didn't want
to hate Demon Snow.
She'll respond to your words.
Your naivete is beautiful.
Kyouka-chan!
Demon Snow!
It's no use, give it up!
Akutagawa!
Don't tell me what to do!
I won't let you get away this time.
This is it.
This joy I feel over death.
Do you feel it?
What the...
Show me once more that glimmer that
opposes all special abilities!
Beautiful.
This is the supreme special ability.
No!
What?
That's not an ability.
That's me!
I understand everything, now.
Why I'm here,
why you appeared before me,
and what his words mean...
You...
You must be the angel who saves me.
The singularity and fog have
been confirmed eradicated.
The Clock Tower esquires have called to
inform us that their mission has been aborted.
What a shame.
The scent of a burning
nation goes well with tea.
What the hell are you doing here?
Dimwit Dazai is safe.
Yo.
Give me your shoulder.
I'm not gifted, and I'm back here,
which must mean it all worked out well.
Atsushi's gotten pretty good.
Don't you think, Dazai?
Atsushi-kun, what I did earlier...
You...
You tried to protect this city.
Do I look like such a good person?
Sure, why?
Well, whatever.
I hope he managed to fill
his boredom and loneliness.
Is this really what you wanted?
Just as Shibusawa was able to forget
he'd been killed before,
I think Dazai can put his
past behind him again.
But this is right.
At least, for now, I'm proud we
were able to protect the city together.
I think it's at least a little more beautiful to
live on with you and Kyouka-chan and the others.
You!
Boneheads! You're still alive!
Everyone's safe.
Of course.
We're the Armed Detective Agency, after all.
Right?
Yes.
It's a minor miracle that,
after all that happened,
none of the civilians were harmed.
Ow!
Get to work, please, Tsujimura-kun.
It's still day four of our
all-nighter marathon.
There's no way we're going to cover this up.
Report
Even though it happened in the conceded zone
of Yokohama, they caused some spectacular damage.
Senpai,
what do you think the deal was
with this incident, anyway?
I don't know.
Given the complexity of the three masterminds'
motivations, we still don't have a full picture.
Dazai-kun's the same as usual, and demon
Fyodor's intentions are impossible to comprehend.
But, beyond all the scheming and lying,
the incident may  fundamentally be very simple.
How is a man like Shibusawa,
so intelligent that others look like alien
creatures to him, to act, to be destroyed,
or to be saved?
To be one of three aliens in the world,
in isolation and loneliness...
I can't even imagine it.
Tsujimoto-kun?
Were you aware of the trick, Boss?
Dazai-kun was acting on his own,
and I expected he would need your help.
As a forerunner.
So I was an opening act?
Dazai-kun is the star.
And what do I get in return?
The return of order in this city.
The peace of this city, huh?
Good work.
You don't need to thank me.
It was your order.
I'm just doing my job.
Everything is but entertainment.
But in order to end this world,
rife with crime and punishment,
I do need that book.
The blank novel
sleeping in this town.
Do you understand?
Do nothing to insult our clients.
You're the agency's mommy,
aren't you, Kunikida-kun?
Don't overwork yourselves, you two.
Off you go.
Take care.
We're leaving.